Rainbow Conquistalor for You Autumn Journey
So, I'm at home, but just in case, let's say hello.
Yes, I'm Kirino Yuu, a.k.a. Bippi.
Yes, I'm Akari Nakamura aka Akarin
Yes, I'm Moe Tsurumi aka Moe-chan
Yes, I'm Shizuko aka Rikopin
Yes, I am Karin Matoda aka Karin
Yes, I would like to introduce you to the five of us.
This time, we will talk for the official Niji no Conquistalor YouTube!
Yay!
For the Niji Conquistadors channel?
We also have the same Akita version on the official ANA YouTube channel, so please check that channel too!
It was a lot of fun!
Yes, it was a lot of fun!
It's a little bit more relaxed here.
Oh, no, it's okay.
No?
You sure?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not a funny talk, guys.
It's not about the missile.
I'm looking forward to an interesting talk.
No, I'm afraid.
Now, about this trip...
We traveled to Akita as a fan club only event in collaboration with ANA Akita.
How was it?
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
I knew it.
It made you feel at home.
That's right.
It's been a while since I've felt happy and relaxed.
It's been a while since I've had any kind of peace and quiet.
I wonder if there was something...
I loved it.I kind of loved it.
Away from the hustle and bustle of this time.
Yeah.
Next week, it's that time.
So, we played a live show at Club Swindle on the first night of Anatabi, do you guys remember that?
Of course. It was quite unique, wasn't it?
We were so close to the audience that we could see their faces when we were performing.
It had the weight of a live concert hall. You could see each and every face.
I could see perfectly to the people in the back. That's for sure.
It was fun. We toured the country half by half,
I think there were a lot of people who only saw one of the groups.
It was the first time for them to see the other group's live show.
It was the same for us. We had never seen the other group's live performance,
We had never seen a live performance by a different group before, so we were like, "Oh, they are doing it in this formation and at this timing.
And, actually, at this concert, the members of Night Breeze introduced themselves to the audience,
Do you remember it? It was the first time.
It was the first time in Yoru Kaze. To the three of us.
There is a VTR there.
Oh, there is!
This is the first time for me to introduce myself at a live concert,
I love you.
You!
I am Music Conmo, Odakuken, Yokase, and Yu Kawabata.
Please give me your best regards.
I made it, and I'd like to do it for the first time.
If you say you can do it...
Please tell me you can do it!
You can fall in love with Mayu, right?
I can do it!
I'm going to be cute today too!
I'm Mayu Kurihara, the cute and innocent Mayu-chan from Nijikon
I'm Mayu Kurihara and I'm a cute little Mayu-chan from Nijikon, and I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
What shall I do?
Wow!
What? Before Osaka?What? By Osaka?
Oh.
Now?
I can go!
Excuse me.
Can I borrow you for the day?
Sure!
You'll be fine with me today, right?
We're going to do the show today, right?
Yes!
Yes, I'm Kirari Sawamura.
I'm Kirari Sawamura, 19 years old.
I'll try to introduce myself.
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Yay!
Yes, Kiririkiri Kiririkiri
Kiritampo
Oh, sorry.
Oh, I didn't tell you.
Well, today...
Excuse me, can I have it in a kiritampo?
It's tomorrow.
Let me try one more time.
Thank you very much.
I'll take it.
Kiririririririririririririri.
Kiritampo.
We'll do our best again today.
This is Mewpico and Kirinomew.
Pleased to meet you.
Congratulations!
Yes! Sending moe to the world!
Receiving!
I'm a bald girl who loves to eat! I'm Moe Tsurumi, aka Moe-chan!
Thank you!Thank you!
Thank you!!!
You're so cute!
Scary!
You're scaring me! Stop it!
There's a side of me that's a bald girl.
I'll do it so you'll never know.
I'm totally comfortable with that.
Why are you doing this?
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Until Moemi Tsurumi's "raw bald girl"...
Cute
Cute.
Oh, I dropped my hair.
I've been taking pictures of my bald face backstage to make it look even more like a bald man.
I kept trying to make it look even more like a bald guy.
I was really scared of that.
No, because I'm a raw bald girl.
And the bald girl is a little bit crazy.
Why?
I don't even know what a bald girl is.
No, no, no, no.
I don't want to be talked to by Kiritampo.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So I thought, "Kiritampo, you can do it, right? I was just thinking like that.
But instead of telling the fans...
I was like, "Can't you call me Kiritanpo? I said "Kiritampo.
And then we said it as a group.
The fans laughed so much.
Some of them said they were tired of it and didn't come to the show.
I even saw a few people on Twitter saying they were bored and didn't come.I saw a little bit of it on Twitter.
They said they wanted to see a version of "Kiritampo" today.
Some people said they wanted to see it.
I was so happy that they filmed it.
So, please come to the camera.
May I?
Here I go!
Kiri kiri kiri kiri.
Kiri, kiri, kiri, kiri, kiri, kiri, kiri, kiri.
I'll do my best with Kiri today, too.
This is Miyu and Kiri Miyu.
Yay!
If I do that from now on
I'll turn into Kiri-tampo!
I'm so scared!
Kiri!
I'll just be a little dandelion.
I don't want to talk about us.
VUVC
You were introduced.
Was this your first time performing in front of everyone?
Yes, in the live show where we are divided into teams.
I've only performed it once or so at the live shows where we are divided into teams.
But we were working on it during this tour.
This time was also a franchise tour, so it was a bit different from the usual tour.
I think the atmosphere was more intimate than usual.
The atmosphere was warmer and more intimate than usual.
There was a warm atmosphere.
So we felt we could unveil the new album without any worries.
You know, Yu-chan...
Ai na VUVC...
I thought you were really good at it.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
I thought of it myself.
How do you like it?
Aww...Ehhhhh!
That's amazing!
You're just a nerd, aren't you?
You're right, you're right.
There's space.
She really wants you to say You Love You.
That's right.
But we all say "You" together.
I don't like it that way.
Oh, yeah!
It kind of reminds me of the first time.
Right?
It's like...
It's my first time.
My first time!
When I turned 13.
Okay, let's try this with some moves.
You wanna stand?
Don't pull.
Just do it right.
How I felt when I was 13...
Twin tails.
The twin tails of decay.
From the voice
Ha ha ha ha
Tuning
Here we go!
The youngest 13 year old from Saitama Prefecture!
You can call me Master Callie if you like.
Callie-sama!
I love dancing and pickled plums.
I love dancing and pickled plums!
I'm looking forward to meeting you!
See, that's how it's going to be!
See!
I get so mad!I'm gonna be mad.
That's right.
I remember... introducing myself to Akari.
I've never seen you before.
Shall we do it?
Let's do it!
Let's do it.
All right. - All right.
Ready?
BinBinBin AkarinBin
I want to be the one to bring smiles to everyone's faces.
I'm 16 years old, from Chiwa prefecture. My name is Akari Nakamura, aka Akarin.
Akari-chan!
Back then, I was afraid to say, "Put me down!
I was afraid to say it.
Next, the second day of the meeting...
The second day, we rented out Akita Jomon Gou for a fan meeting.
Oh, yeah. Remember that?
Yes, I remember.
That's where you get to interact with the fans the most.
A lot of them came.
But we had our own cars.
You were in a separate caravan.
What did you do? What did you do?
Question time.
And Akari.
Suddenly, they were talking about what they liked about each member of the car.
Akari has to work hard.
I don't think we'll get to see that scene.
I heard there's a scene.
Let's watch the VR.
What would you like to do on the flight home?
What do you want to do on the flight home?
I'm also wondering who's going to be next to me on the way home... but I'd like to return Zoo-chan's observation diary to you...
Yesterday...Yesterday...
Yesterday, I was invited to join the students for dinner.
We had dinner together, and it was so much fun.
She had a thick face with Ayane Okada.
Ayane Okada asked me to go out with her.
She'd tell anyone to go out with her.
But Miyuki said she asked me to marry her too.
Don't be fooled.
Recently, I was able to go on a tour with the other participants.
Riyu Hinata...
I asked Riyu Hinata if she'd like to go for a beef like this.
She said no, but it's a bit difficult, so I wanted to clarify.
Let's go eat beef together.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Okay.
Have you had gyoza yet?
No, I haven't.
Of course you haven't.
You forgot.
You remembered when you saw me.
Megumi's been trying to get involved, too.
But we never talked about dumplings.
I think she's forgotten, too.
Don't worry about me.
She'll never go.
I'll go. I like gyoza.
He likes gyoza. He's talking about Ayame.
Has anyone ever asked Ayame to go out with them?
Have any of you ever been asked to go out with Ayame?
Any of them?
I want you to marry me.
Don't you love Akarin too?
She says she'll do it like a cat.
She calls me...
Say "meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meowSay meow meow meow.
She's a bad girl.
I am.
You really are like a big sister.
If only Akarin was my big sister.
I wish she was my big sister.
I'm like...
I can talk to her about anything.
Like we're super friends.
I was just listening to your episode.
I've been thinking...
What's that? That?
Huh? That's funny.
Then, to all the fans.
And then he gave us a boxed lunch.
We had time to eat it, too.
It was delicious.
Here we go.
Moe's trivia
This is the first time I've seen it here.
By the way, it's only here.
I'm only going to cover it once.
I'll take it away from you.
Can I do it again?
Moe's Tidbits
Moe's Tidbits.
Yes!
Looks good.
Actually
Moe's Bento
It's called Ueno Shokudo Otsumami Bento
It was created as a project of a big TV program
Akita Nairiku Line
Akita Nairiku Line's original iron rice
Well...
Do you have any suggestions on what was good?Do you have any suggestions on what you enjoyed?
Losing sushi
Chicken
Sushi marinated in koji miso
It was delicious!
Red vinegar and red miso
You mentioned akasuzubeni earlier, too.
I can vividly remember the taste.
I know, I know.
It has a strong taste.
It's like a drink or something.
That's right.
It's a snack box.
Well, here we go again.
I'll show you a video of the food report.
Please take a look.
Bento time!
It's so delicious!
So many colors!
Delicious!
Great!
Bento time!
Kilsayan
Yum!
This is the Ibri school!
Really?
That's awesome! It's the Ibri school!
It's a school for itinerant tabloids! - It's a school for itinerant tabloids!
I love it!
Bon appétit!
Sounds great!
Smoky aroma
wonderful!
makes me want to drink sake.
It's been served in Akita for a long time, or at a rice restaurant or something, but I think I'll probably like it.
It's out now!There you go.
I've had it three times since I came to Akita, so I guess it's famous.
It's so delicious!
It's good.
The container is amazing.
It really is.
The weather in Akita is really nice!
It's great!
It's very rich.
What's in it?
The guy at the store said there's a selfie video.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I heard it.
Is it a selfie?
She said it was a selfie.
Wow!
But it's a really nice bento.
Any kind of food can come in here.
I want to hear Yuka-chan's food report!
I want to hear your food report!
So cute!
What's this?
I've never heard of it.
I've been curious.
Oh, it's sushi rice.
It has a certain aroma.
I like it.
Specialty
Ya!
Purigakko
Nice sound
Sounds good
I wanted to try this one too.
This is so much better.
I haven't caught up.I haven't caught up.
I wish I could just eat it all.
I'm eating it with miso
It's pretty good when you get it.
That's great.
I'm catching up.
On the contrary...
My head hasn't caught up.
It was the other way around.
It's been a while since I've had any ASMR.
Please do it.
Bon appétit.
How's it going?
It's great.
And it's...
Yum! Yum!
Freshly opened eyes.
Rich in color
rich in color
full of cheers
what's with all this twirling?
pre-gakko
Oh no!
Yee-haw!
Yummy!
He made Zoo-chan eat it!
I'm so happy!
It was a very unique food report, wasn't it?
The whole thing is very loose.
Between "off" and "on".
That's the normal atmosphere.
I wish I could have seen it.
You know, with this kind of thing.
There was an ebullient outbreak.There was an outbreak of ibringer clabrin.
About three.
Three or four.
I knew I was working with ASMR.
But you know what?
I'd like to reiterate to everyone who's watching this
In order to convey a sense of realism
I'd like to remind you of that delicious bento
I'd like to have a real food report showdown.
It'll be fun!
Is it?
Yes, it is.
I know you have it.
I have it. I have it. I have it.
What?
You're kidding, right?
The moment you see a lie, you imagine it.
I've been thinking.
No, but...
What?
You said earlier that it was moving very fast.
By the way, I'll be chairing the jury.
What?
I'm just trying to set an example for the relicer.
Yes, of course.
Everyone's going to get a piece of it.
I'll give you something if you win.
What?
You're lying.
No, it's not.
You're kidding.
Moe Tsurumi, the princess of food reportage, says she's been approved.
I don't like it at all.
I'm scared.
It's draining.Consumption.
I don't like it.
Yes, I mean...
I'm going to do it.
By force.
Yes, sir.
Each of you tell me what you're going to eat.
Tell me what you're going to eat.
In what order?
I'll go.
Oh!
That's great.
So...
The First Annual Food Repo Grand Rounds!
Yay!
Let's start with Kiminomiyu's food report.
What would you like to eat?
Shiitake mushrooms
Shiitake mushroom
Okay, okay.
Okay, we'll go to Kiminomiyu's food report.
Three, two, one.
Yes, I'd like to try the shiitake mushrooms that were in the bento.
I'd like to try some of the shiitake mushrooms that were in the bento.
Bon appétit.
The shiitake mushrooms are flavorful, juicy and delicious.
Not bamboo?
Not the tasty bamboo?
Delicious bamboo!
Yes, thank you.
We've been waiting for you, haven't we?
You've been wondering when you're going to use it.
I have that too.
Next, Akari Nakamura, what would you like to eat?
Kasubeni.Kasveni.
Even Akari Nakamura's food report.
Three, two, one.
Yes, you see this?
This is a fish called "Kasubeni.
There's something behind it, like a bone, a little crispy.
I wonder if it's edible?
I wonder.
Can you eat it?
Well, let's eat first.
Bon appétit!
So many comments.
It's so delicious! The flavor is so rich, it'll make your rice go faster!
Delicious!
It's like crispy. I ate it.
It was really crispy!
Okay, then, what would you like to eat, Miko Shimizu?
Chicken.
And now, to Miko Shimizu's food report. Three, two, one.
I showed you. I showed you.
You have presence.
Wow!
Beautiful.
The color
There's no stopping it.
It smells so good.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
It's chewier than I expected.
It's kind of crunchy like this.
My teeth are bouncing around in here.
It's just very tasty.
No, no, no, no, no.
You can't taste it at all.
Maybe you're curious about it.
If you're curious, please try it.If you are interested, please try it.
Well, let's continue.
I'll stuff the bird.
What would you like to eat?
At the Iburi School.
Here it comes! Here it comes!
We'll now go to Hanashi Watanabe's food report.
Three, two, one.
Look at this bento!
There are a lot of ingredients in here.
But this one really caught my eye.
Here it is!
Look at the pickled radish from the Iburi School!
I can already smell it from here.
There are a lot of ingredients.
I'd say it's very astringent.
It smells a little off-putting, doesn't it?
Then I'd like to have this.
Please listen. Coins. Also a coin.
Do you see the pores?
I hear it! A loud noise!
Hmmm! I have a very good intuition,
And the aroma of the stomach is so good that it goes straight to my nose,
It's not something I can usually eat right away, so I'm glad it's in my lunch box.
I'm glad to have it in my bento.
I have eaten a lot of giburi since I came to Akita.
So long!
Mmm! Delicious!
Oh, wow!
I'll never get a job as a food reporter!
Okay, so here we go,
Who is the winner of the first food report showdown?
Durrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
D'urrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Matobakarin!
Thank you very much!Thank you!
I thought I had it!
Well, as expected, I thought it was too royal, but, you know, I couldn't choose.
C, C is different.
It was a little different.
If it had been only C, there was still a possibility that I would have waited.
So, that was the first food report showdown!
Yes, well, this time is coming to an end,
How was your trip to Akita with your fans?
It was a lot of fun,
Oh, yes!
I've heard the frustration of those who couldn't make it, so I'll be very happy if I can stay again.
I'd love to make it a regular event!
We want to make it a regular event!
Yes, we want to make it a regular event!
That would be great!
Well, next time on Rainbow Conquistador for you,
Web5 will take you behind the scenes of the music video shot in the pools and sandy beaches of Shiragaki, Okinawa,
Here we are! We are going to show you,
So, enjoy!
Yes, we went to the swimming pool and Chikasan Rice Beach,
We went to the pool, Chikasan Rice Beach, and other nice places around the area,
So, please enjoy the show and come and see it for yourself,
I hope you will enjoy watching the film, and I hope you will go there by yourself,
If you see it, you will definitely want to make a pilgrimage to the holy land,
You will definitely want to go there!
Summer is coming!
That's right!
You have to go!
What if we don't go?
Yes, I'm sure you all will enjoy the music video and the Nishiko too,
Please watch the next channel!
Seino Conquistadors!
I'm Nishino Conquistador!
Bye bye!Bye bye!